Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 40. 1961, Nov. 1.S.F., Ca. L[ouise] to Kate [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1961, Nov. 18.S.F., Ca. Louise to Kate [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1961, Nov. 22.Los Angeles, Ca. Richfield Oil Corp. (A.S.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1961, Dec. 6.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S. re: pipe line right-of-way., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1961, Dec. 12.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Ralph Kenworthy re: irrigation pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1961, Dec. 13.Los Angeles, Ca. Richfield Oil Corp. (A.S.M.) to Donald May., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1961, Dec. 18.N.P. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to W.W.S. re: Weddell Creek water., T.L.
    - 47. 1961, Dec. 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to John Inglis Frozen Foods Co., re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
  - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - 1. 1962, Jan. 2.S.F., Ca. Division of Housing (L.N.) to Labor Camp Owners & Operators re: Calif. Labor Code, Section 2410.4., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1962, Jan. 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams. (D.O.M.) to Joseph M. Reiter., T.L.
    - 3. 1962, Jan 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co. (E.B.) to Member., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1962, Jan. 23.San Jose, Ca. Gallagher & Rainville (P.T.G.) to Murphy & Adams., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1962, Jan. 23.S.F., Ca. Dept. of Fish & Game (W.A.E.) to C.[B.]S. re: permit to remove harmful species of fish., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1962, Feb. 15.Salinas, Ca. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. re: Steele Ranch tax increase., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1962, Feb. 25.Los Altos Hills, Ca. Alan Brown to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 8. 1962, Feb. 28.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1962, Mar. 3.N.P. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. re: Steele Ranch tax increase., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1962, Mar. 9.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1962, Mar. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Capitola Berry Farms re: Pescadero water district., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1962, Mar. 15.N.P. Acme Farms Co. (R.K.) to Mrs. Hulda McLean., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1962, Mar. 15.N.P. Acme Farms Co. (R.K.) to Mrs. C.G. Willis., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1962, Mar. 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S. re: right-of-way on Kent Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1962, April 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1962, April 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Paul T. Gallagher re: Steele - Capitola Berry Farms Agreement., T.L.
    - 17. 1962, June 5.N.P. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. to Mrs. Hulda McLean & Mrs. C.G. Willis., T.L.
    - 18. 1962, June 7.Felton, Ca. F.I.F. Assc., Inc. (B.C.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1962, June 8.Redwood City, Ca. William G. Phoenix to Donald O. May., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1962, June 8.Same as # 19.
    - 21. 1962, July 27.Redwood City, Ca. Redwood City Tribune (M.[m.]G.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1962, Aug. 21.Redwood City, Ca. Currie, Lebsack, Hannig & Ferrari (C.W.L.) to Donald May., T.L.
    - 23. 1962, Aug. 31.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1962, Sept. 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Gerald B. Ferrari., T.L.
    - 25. 1962, Sept. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1962, Sept. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Currie, Lebsack, Hannig & Ferrari., T.L.
    - 27. Same as # 26.
    - 28. 1962, Sept. 13.Redwood City, Ca. Currie, Lebsack, Hannig & Ferrari to State Water Rights Board., T.L.
    - 29. 1962, Sept. 13.Redwood City, Ca. Currie, Lebsack, Hannig & Ferrari to S. Skeehan., T.L.
    - 30. 1962, Sept. 13.Redwood City, Ca. Currie, Lebsack, Hannig & Ferrari (G.B.F.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1962, Nov. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1962, Nov. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Pacific Gas & Electric Co., T.L.
    - 33. 1962, Dec. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Currie, Lebsack, Hannig & Ferrari., T.L.
    - 34. 1962, Dec. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1963, Jan. 2.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (I.S.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1963, Jan. 14.Aptos, Ca. James H. DuMond to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1963, Jan. 29.N.P. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1963, Feb. 8.Bellville, Texas. C.J. Marik to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1963, Feb. 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1963, Feb. 27.N.P. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1963, Feb. 29.Hollister, Ca. Everett [J. Matthews] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 42. 1963, Mar. 15.S.F., Ca. Louise to Kate [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 43. 1963, Mar. 25.San Mateo, Ca. San Mateo County Historical Assc. (F.M.S.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1963, April 5.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (I.S.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1963, April 11.Sacramento, Ca. Governor Edmund G. Brown to Mrs. W.F.S. re: Public Law 78 - supplemental labor., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1963, May 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co. to Member., T.L.
    - 47. 1963, July 23.Salinas, Ca. Noland Hamerly, Etienne & Fulton (M.E.E.*) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1963, July 26.N.P. Bernard McGavitt to Richfield Oil Corp. re: oil well drilling permit., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1963, July 26.N.P. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 50. 1963, July 27.N.P. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 51. 1963, July 30.Los Angeles, Ca. Richfield Corp. (H.W.S.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 52. 1963, Aug. 20.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co. (E.B.) to Member., T.L.
    - 53. 1963, Oct. 8..Los Angeles, Ca. Richfield Oil Corp. (R.G.D.) to W.W.S. & B.M.S., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1963, Oct. 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1963, Dec. 3.San Jose, Ca. Marlois & Hover (W.H.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 1. 1964, Jan. 2.S.F., Ca. Division of Housing to Labor Camp Owner & Operators re: labor camp registration., T.L.
    - 2. Same as #1.
    - 3. 1964, Jan. 9.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Hank [Sciaroni] to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1964, Jan. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1964, Jan. 16.Honolulu, Hawaii. Gold Hill Realty Inc. (T.C.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1964, Feb. 2.San Carlos, Ca. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.] re: sale of Ranch., A.L.S.
    - 7. 1964, Feb. 7.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to Mrs. W.F.S. re: Green Oak Ranch - profitability., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1964, Feb. 21.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to C.[B.]S. re: sale of stocks., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1964, Mar. 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to Mrs. W.F.S. re: sale of stocks., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1964, Mar. 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1964, Mar. 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1964, April 2.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co. (E.E.W.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1964, April 9.Watsonville, Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (P.Z.) to Joe Alcantara., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1964, April 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Baikie & Alcantara (J.R.A.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1964, April 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. K.J. McGranahan to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1964, April 21.S.F., Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to George Heyashi re: employee housing., T.L.
    - 17. 1964, April 22.N.P. Hank [Sciaroni] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1964, April 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to William G. Phoenix., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1964, April 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Calif. State Auto. Assc. (B.D.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1964, April 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Everett J. Matthews re: sale of Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1964, April 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to Murphy & Adams re: sale of Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1964, May 2.Saratoga, Ca. Ostrowski Assc. (W.E.D.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1964, May 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Rich Lindley., T.L.
    - 24. 1964, May 9.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Emmet L. Rittenhouse., T.L.
    - 25. 1964, May 10.Santa Barbara. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to Ivan G. Parker re: Civil Case - Capitola Berry Farms vs. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1964, May 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1964, June 5.San Carlos, Ca. Rick Lindley to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 28. 1964, June 18.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1964, June 21.San Jose, Ca. Stone & Schulte (W.E.D.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1964, June 25.S.F., Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to C.[B.]S. re: employee housing., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1964, June 29.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to Mrs. W.F.S, T.L.S.
    - 32. 1964, July 1.N.P. Committee for the Tax Proposal to Friend & Neighbor., T.L.
    - 33. 1964, July 6.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1964, July 8.N.P. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 35. 1964, July 9.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1964, July 15.S.F., Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to George Hayashi., T.L.
    - 37. 1964, July 27.Redwood City, Ca. Guide Real Estate (B.A.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1964, July 30.Riverside, Ca. Tom Murton to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1964, July 31.San Carlos, Ca. Rick Lindley to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 40. 1964, Aug. 16.Tucson, Ariz. Alan Brown to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1964, Aug. 19.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Univ. of Calif. Agric. Extension Service (R.H.S.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1964, Aug. 26.S.F., Ca. Brobeck, Phleger & Harrison to Title Insurance & Trust Co. re: legal matters., T.L.
    - 43. 1964, Aug. 28.Redwood City, Ca. County of San Mateo Planning Commission (R.D.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1964, Sept. 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Mrs. Harriet H. Bern re: sale of Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
    - 45. 1964, Sept. 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Tom Murton re: sale of Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
    - 46. 1964, Sept. 14.Redwood City, Ca. Title Insur. & Trust Co. (S.P.H.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 47. 1964, Oct. 17.S.F., Ca. Phoebe Barkan to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 48. 1964, Oct. 28.Salinas, Ca. Monterey County Historical Society (H.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1964, Nov. 5.San Carlos, Ca. R.H. Sciaroni to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 50. 1964, Nov. 18.Monterey, Ca. Pauline McCleary to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1964, Dec. 4.S.F., Ca. Dept. of Health, Education & Welfare (D.H.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 52. 1964, Dec. 14.Monterey, Ca. Dept. of Parks & Recreation (J.T.C.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 53. 1964, Dec. 21.El Cerrito, Ca. Catherine Kerr to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1964, Dec. 21.San Jose, Ca. Albert T. Henley to William G. Phoenix re: DuMond vs. Steele - settlement of cross-compalint., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1964, Dec. 22.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - 1. 1965,N.P. Kay Kerr to Unknown [C.B.S.]., A.N.S.
    - 2. 1965, Jan.San Carlos, Ca. John S. Lewis., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1965, Feb. 2.Monterey, Ca. Division of Beaches & Parks (R.W.R.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1965, Feb. 20.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to [C.B.]S., A.N.S.
    - 5. 1965, Mar. 4.Belmont, Ca. Sister [Gaoriel], Sister _____(?) & Sister _____(?) (College of Notre Dame) to [C.B.]S., T.N.S.
    - 6. 1965, Mar. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. To C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1965, Mar. 26.Monterey, Ca. Division of Beaches & Parks (R.W.R.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1965, April 5.Same as # 3.
    - 9. 1965, April 17.Santa Barbara, Ca. W.W.S. to William G. Phoenix re: civil case - DuMond vs. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1965, May 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1965, May 7.Felton, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. to Hillman B. Walker., T.L.
    - 12. 1965, May 7.Same as # 11.
    - 13. 1965, May 7.Same as # 11.
    - 14. 1965, May 12.Santa Barbara, Ca. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to William G. Phoenix re: civil case - DuMond vs. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1965, May 12.Santa Barbara, Ca. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to Mrs. C.G. Willis re: Waddell Creek Water Agreement., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1965, May 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to William G. Phoenix., T.L.
    - 17. 1965, May 18.Santa Cruz, Ca. Ivan G. Parker to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1965, May 20.N.P. Hank [Sciaroni] to Assemblyman Leo J. Ryan re: sale of Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1965, June 14.Half Moon Bay, Ca. San Mateo County Farm Bureau (W.E.) to Farm Land Owner., T.L.S
    - 20. 1965, June 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1965, July 3.Half Moon Bay, Ca. San Mateo County Farm Bureau (W.H.E.) to Farm Bureau Members and Land Owners.re: county assessed valuation for tax pruposes., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1965, July 26.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (P.N.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1965, July 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to W.W.S. re: sale of Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
    - 24. 1965, July 28.Santa Barbara, Ca. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to Donald O. May. re: Capitola Berry Farms vs. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1965, Aug. 4.Salinas, Ca. Louise Todd to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 26. 1965, Aug. 12.Sacramento, Ca. Ron Leineke to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1965, Aug. 31.Sacramento, Ca. Ron Leineke to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1965, Sept. 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Unknown [C.B.S.] to Mr. Willis re: ranch procedures., A.L.
    - 29. 1965, Sept. 17.Sacramento, Ca. State Water Rights Board (L.K.H.) to C.B.S. re: water rights - Waddell Creek., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1965, Sept. 27.Saint Ignace, Mich. Louise to Mrs. W.F.S., P.C.S.
    - 31. 1965, Sept. 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Lewis J. Macchia re: right-of-way deed with Ocean Shore Railroad Co., T.L.
    - 32. 1965, Oct. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to George Davidson re: sale of Steele Ranch (Green Oaks Ranch)., T.L.
    - 33. 1965, Oct. 21.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to C.B.S. re: sales of Steele Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1965, Oct. 21.San Mateo, Ca. San Mateo Co. Dept. of Public Health & Welfare (E.M.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1965, Nov. 6.Sierra Madre, Ca. [Mrs. Cornelius G. Willis] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1965, Nov. 11.S.F., Ca. Feldman, Waldman & Kline (R.B.M.) to Donald May re: Gregoire - Steele transaction, lease., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1965, Nov. 16.Vallejo, Ca. Dept. of Water Resources (C.A.M.) to R.H. Sciaroni., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1965, Nov. 19.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Univ. of Calif. Agric. Extension Service (R.H.S.) to C.[B]S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1965, Dec. 29.Cleveland, O. Grace & Jack McCord to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - 1. 1966.N.P. The [Clark] Kerrs to [C.B.S.]., A.N.S.
    - 2. 1966, Jan. 22.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1966, Jan. 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S, T.L.S.
    - 4. 1966, Jan. 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1966, Mar. 24.McCord, Alaska. Grace [McCord] to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1966, Mar. 25.N.P. Stephen Wyckoff to Edmund G. Brown., T.L.
    - 7. 1966, Mar. 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Lodge No. 824 (B.S.A.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1966, April 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1966, April 26.Sacramento, Ca. Covernor Edmund G. Brown to Donald O. May., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1966, May 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (J.F.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1966, July 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Raymond H. Goodrich to Mrs. W.F.S, T.L.S.
    - 12. 1966, Sept. 2.San Carlos, Ca. Rick Lindley to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 13. 1966, Nov. 21.Santa Cruz, Ca. Adams & Levin (E.J.A.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1966, Dec. 24.San Luis Qbispo, Ca. San Luis Obispo County Historical Society (L.C.D.) to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 15. 1967. Jan. 8.Albuquerque, New Mexico. Grace [McCord] to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1967, Jan. 22.Hillsborough, Ca. Pacific Mariculture, Inc. (W.W.B.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1967, Jan. 30.Berkeley, Ca. David [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1967, Feb. 1.Santa Cruz, Ca. Adams & Levin (E.J.A.) to State Water Rights Board., T.L.
    - 19. 1967, Mar. 21.Santa Cruz, Ca. Adams & Levin (E.J.A.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1967, Mar. 24.Hillsborough, Ca. Phoebe Gilpin to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1967, May 29.Cleveland, Ohio. Grace [McCord] to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 22. 1967, June 2.Redwood City, Ca. San Mateo Co. Title Co. (F.D.) to Eugene J. Adams re: sale of Steele Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1967, Aug. 15.Redwood City, Ca. County of San Mateo Board of Supervisors (J.F.*) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1967, Sept. 21.Union, N.J. Unidentified to Mrs. W.[F.]S., P.C.S.
    - 25. 1967, Sept. 30.Redwood City, Ca. Marian Goodman to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1967, Oct. 14.Redwood City, Ca. Marian Goodman to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1967, Dec. 4.Hampton, Va. I.G. Fremont to Mrs. W.[F.]S., A.L.S.
    - 28. 1967, Dec. 15.N.P. Ralph & Tom Wilson to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1967, Dec. 22.Redwood City, Ca. San Mateo County Title Co. (F.D.) to C.B.S. re: sale of Steele Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1968, Jan. 2.Redwood City, Ca. Sequoia Nat'l. Bank (R.H.T.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1968, Mar. 6.[Pescadero, Ca.]. Juanita Alving to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1968, May 17.Sacramento, Ca. Calif. Exposition (R.A.N.) to Green Oak Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1968, May 22.Sunnyvale, Ca. Lorna (Staley) Esry to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1968, May 23.N.P. Louise B. Elm to Mrs. Esry., A.L.S.
    - 35. 1968, Aug. 5.Redwood City, Ca. County of San Mateo Park & Recreation Commission (R.H.S.*) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1968, Aug. 8.S.F., Ca. Junior League of S.F., Inc. to Historical Society Member., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1968, Aug. 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Adams & Levin (E.J.A.) to State Water Resources Control Board., T.L.
    - 38. 1968, Sept. 2.N.P. Hulda [McClean] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 39. 1968, Nov. 8.Washington, D.C. Paul N. McCloskey, Jr. to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1969,N.P. Catherine Kerr to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1969, Jan. 1.N.P. Helen Lengfield to Friend [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1969, Jan. 9.Sacramento, Ca. Division of Water Rights (K.L.W.) to W.W.S., T.L.
    - 43. 1969, Jan. 30.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (R.L.A.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1969, May 15.N.P. Martha Shelton to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 45. 1969, Aug. 31.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.] re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1969, Sept. 8.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 47. 1969, Sept. 11.Davis, Ca. C.L. Pelissier, Extension Dairyman - Univ. of Calif. Agric. Extension Service, to R.H. Sciaroni re: identification of dairy machinery., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1969, Sept. 19.N.P. Dr. Harold Alvarez to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 49. 1969, Sept. 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Ruth Kay Collins to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1969, Nov. 1.Hampton Va. Unidentified to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 51. 1969, Dec. 1.N.P. Robert N. Mackinnon to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.
    - 52. 1969, Dec. 11.[Point Reyes Station]. Jack Mason to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 1. 1970, Jan. 8.New Orleans, La. [Mrs. Jack H. Stocker] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1970, Jan. 12.New Orleans, La. [Mrs. Jack H. Stocker] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1970, Jan. 13.Monterey, Ca. Martha [Bentley] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 4. 1970, Mar. 14.N.P. Hank [Sciaroni] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 5. 1970, April 22.Hillsborough, Ca. Fay to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1970, May 19.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Spanishtown Historical Society (Mrs. R.G.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1970, Aug. 6.Berkeley, Ca. David to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1970, Aug. 13.Austin, Texas. Texas State Library (J.M.K.) to Mildred Lee Damon., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1970, Aug. 14.Pescadero, Ca. Heola(?) to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 10. 1970, Aug. 19.Dragerton, Utah. Ruth [Bradley] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1970, [Aug.] 19.N.P. [Dragerton, Utah]. Brad [Bradley]. to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1970, Aug. 28.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank to Holder of P.G. & E. Co. 1st and Refunding Mortgage Bonds., T.L.
    - 13. 1970, Aug. 31.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1970, Sept. 1.Santa Cruz, Ca. C[B.]S. to Office of the County Clerk., A.L.S.
    - 15. 1970, Sept. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Municipal Court (D.O.M.) to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1970, Sept. 13.N.P. Harold & Vi to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1970, Sept. 17.San Carlos, Ca. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.] re: taxes - coast land., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1970, Sept. 24.Indianapolis, Indiana. Dorothy to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1970, Oct. 8.S.F., Ca. Grand Lodge Free & Accepted Masons of Calif. (E.H.S.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1970, Oct. 28.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1970, Nov. 4.Sallisaw, Okla. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 22. 1970, Nov. 16.Palo Alto, Ca. Celia(?) Ostrander to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 23. 1970, Nov. 17.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.] re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1970, Dec. 1.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.] re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1970, Dec. 6.So. Lake Tahoe, Ca. Kethy to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 26. 1970, Dec. 14.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1970, Dec. 28.N.P. Grand Lodge Free & Accepted Masons of Calif. (E.H.S.) to Wilfred H. Steele., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 1. 1971, Jan. 23.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1971, Jan. 28.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1971, Feb. 12.Stockton, Ca. Joanne Pinkham to W.H.Steele., A.N.S.
    - 4. 1971, Feb. 17.San Jose, Ca. [Wilfred] to C.[B.S.]. frag., T.L.
    - 5. 1971, Feb. 21.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1971, Feb. 21.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1971, Feb. 23.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1971, Feb. 24.Same as # 7.
    - 9. 1971, Feb. 27.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.] re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1971, Mar. 1.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1971, Mar. 2.San Luis Obispo, Ca. Louisiana Dart, Curator to [C.B.]S. re: genealogy., P.C.S.
    - 12. 1971, Mar. 2.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1971, Mar. 3.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1971, Mar. 8.Amherst, Ohio. Marion [Steele] to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 15. 1971, Mar. 9.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1971, Mar. 10.[Berkeley, Ca.]. Dorothy [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1971, Mar. 16.Riviera, Arizona. Brad & Ruth [Bradley] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1971, Mar. 18.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 19. [1971], Mar. 19.Hillsborough, Ca. Fay to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1971, Mar. 20.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1971, Mar. 24.Same as # 20.
    - 22. 1971, Mar. 24.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (G.L.H.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1971. Mar. 27.Same as # 20.
    - 24. 1971, Mar. 30.San Mateo, Ca. San Mateo County Historical Assc. (L.O.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1971, Mar. 31.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]. re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1971, April 2.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1971, April 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Ruth Kay Collins to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1971, April 14.[Berkeley Ca.]. [Dorothy Harding] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.
    - 29. 1971, April 16.Monterey, Ca. (M.F.F.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1971, April 18.Tucumari, N.M. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 31. 1971, April 21.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 32. 197, April 21.Half Moon Bey, Ca. Agric. Extension Service, Univ. of Calif., San Mateo County to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.